Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
With elf spirits possessing the bodies of magic knights and attacking humans, the royal capital found itself mired in chaos.
Inside the Eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout, Luck and some of the others turned against their fellow royal knights.
And Asta's words about finding common ground weren't enough to convince Raya to stop the violence from unfolding further.
Let's foster understanding.
There were no lies in anything that he said, and so I trusted him.
And what did it get me?
That.
So you see, I'm done with trusting.
Ryl, is that you?
Hey Raya! Good to see ya!
Raya!
All of them, too?
We won't last five minutes against them.
After pulling Asta and Zora from the fight for their own safety,
Marilyona faced their foes alone.
You seem like a benevolent leader, Madam Royal.
You don't understand a thing, do you?
I sent those novices home because they were getting in my way.
Slow you down.
Don't make me laugh.
I wanted the chance to obliterate all of you personally!
I want you personally!
Wiedersehen.
and
What is your body?
I feel you're feeling your feet
I'm in the blue sky in the sky
The sky is bright and blue
The way you're crying and cry
I'm waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting
Don't leave me alone
I'm going to fly away
I'm going to try again
I'm waiting, waiting, waiting
Unlike the same part
I want an eye on the glasses
Your tears are sitä
I want to hear your feelings
That's the essence!
I'm not Stephanie
Baby Rising
What in the world's happening out there?
I'm not sure. All I know is we have to keep Surfway Goleon safe.
That's the best you humans can do? You're useless, even as a group.
What's gotten into you, Vice-Captain Randall? Please stop this!
Not going to happen. I'll keep fighting until every one of you humans is destroyed.
And besides, my name's not Randall, so stop calling me that.
His magic power is insanely strong!
It's no use. We're dead. There's no way we can win.
Don't give me that!
Did you forget?
We were trained by the two greatest Magic Knight Captains who ever lived.
We are the proud and mighty squad known as the Crimson Lion Kings!
Giving up and losing are two things we don't do!
Are you sure about that?
I've saturated the entire area with air magic.
And as such, you can't even cast a proper spell.
Randall always used to add air to my flame magic to fan the fire and make my abilities more powerful.
Who knew we would be such a tough enemy?
Doesn't matter. I'll win and bring you back to your senses!
Focus.
Flame magic!
Viral flame!
Look at that! You did manage it!
But unfortunately, I have air magic.
Air blockade!
Don't bother with those puny flames. I'll just blow them out like a candle.
Now, air magic! Crushing air blast technique!
Come on!
Leo!
Come on, be a good boy. It'll be easier for everyone if you would just drop dead already.
I'm not gonna lose.
The fire of the Crimson Lion Kings can never be put out.
Not by you or anyone!
I'm with Leo on this one.
We'll combine the strength of all our senior ranked mages.
Let's remind our Vice Captain who he really is!
Right!
I say we start off with my iron creation magic, iron bullet!
And flame magic, burst javelin!
Try stone magic, solid rock spell!
We'll show you the valor of the Crimson Lion Kings!
You humans are a stubborn bunch.
No matter how many of you come at me at once, you're all done for.
You can't run!
It's time to take care of the other side.
Air magic.
Explosive air weight, Paul!
14!
He moves his body through the sky by kicking, then he attacks with invisible chunks of the atmosphere itself.
Talk about a solid strategy. No one can touch him.
Air magic.
Crushing air blast!
Even a team of senior ranked mages isn't enough to defeat him now.
If only Sir Foygolion could help...
Don't say that!
Our skills are being put to the test.
This time, we're the ones who need to protect him.
Stay strong, mages!
If we can survive this barrage, then we have a chance to counter!
No, you won't.
Found you!
Trained by the best, huh?
It sure didn't help you much.
That's it!
Thought you'd take me by surprise, did you?
It seemed like you were beginning to cooperate, but you were just waiting for your shot.
Here, this'll show you.
Now, air magic crushing air blast!
Don't trust your eyes. Feel it!
He dodged it!
Well.
With so much mana here, the most effective way to win against air magic is to read the mana itself.
I may have been standing by, but it wasn't out of fear.
I'm starting to observe more and more.
I've come to understand the calm within the flame.
Don't get cocky over a little fluke.
Air magic exclusive air wave palm!
Your attack hit mine head on, which cut their damages in half.
And you immediately cast the flame chaser as I was dodging the impact.
Perhaps it wasn't a fluke then.
Great skill and fast growth.
Just what I expect from someone with royal blood.
You can say that again.
Leo, there's no doubt you're going to become the leader of this squad someday.
So let us buy you a little time.
Please, get out of this place and live.
Take the wounded with you.
Guys, no.
We're teammates.
I can stay and fight by your side.
Run.
Hurry.
Our squad's counting on you.
We are the honorable and courageous Crimson Lion Kings.
So for the sake of our comrades and the nation we love,
we will eliminate this threat without fear.
Yes, sir.
Gareth.
I can't just abandon you.
We'll all survive this battle together.
It's so close.
I can almost reach out and touch it.
But my body won't.
Leo!
Your breakthrough came a moment too late, I'm afraid.
As you can see by your sudden inability to stand,
using an unfamiliar fighting style like that as a drain on the old stamina.
And you're supposed to be their leader one day?
Well, I'll just ensure that day never comes.
Damn it!
No!
Come on, body, move!
Don't do it!
Soon, all humans will die brutal deaths, especially royals like you.
I won't give up!
How could I?
I made a promise!
There's no way I'm gonna die!
Not now!
Not here!
Come on!
Please stand up!
Whoa!
What kind of weird mana is this?
Where'd that come from?
More enemies?
No.
It feels warm.
Like a flame that's enveloping everything.
You fought well, Leo.
I'm proud.
I can't believe you're here.
But you have much to learn.
Stay back.
I'll handle this.
That mana, it feels so familiar.
Salamander?
How did you...
As head of the Crimson Lion Kings, and as your older brother, I will be bested no more!
Where am I?
I feel it.
The blazing mana of Leo and the others.
I have to come to their aid.
It's my responsibility.
Both as a magic knight, and as the captain of our brave squad.
Can't you not endure?
Is this the extent of your so-called power?
Fue go le on for millions!
Could this be...
The fire spirit, Salamander?
From now on, I won't allow anyone to stand in my way.
Though I may have lost my arm, though flames may scorch my body, as long as there are people waiting for me.
The captain of the Crimson Lion Kings, Fue go le on vermilion, will press on!
What's this?
It fills me with both life and mana.
Perhaps there's something left that I'm meant to do.
Is that what you're telling me?
Fire spirit, mark my words.
I swear to use your power well.
I apologize for the delay.
It's all right.
I knew my brother wouldn't let a scratch like that keep him away forever.
All of you have thought valiantly.
Even while I was deep in slumber, the brilliant blazing of your mana was able to reach me.
Thank goodness you're alive!
Right.
That's the fire spirit, Salamander.
Asla said it used to be partnered with a top member of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Then one day it just disappeared in the middle of a battle.
My brother is honest and determined.
He has a trusted reputation.
He's a grand magic knight and the eldest son of the royal house vermilion.
When you put all those things together, why wouldn't Salamander have wanted him?
A human for a partner?
How is that possible?
And a royal at that.
They're the most corrupt of them all.
Randall!
I've just awakened so my flames may be unruly.
Stand firm so you won't be consumed.
Is that so?
Even if you were chosen by a spirit, you're still pathetic human trashed.
No matter what you do, you'll never outmatch an elf!
You've got this!
Casting flame spirit magic, Salamander's breath!
These flames are too powerful!
I can't blow them out!
I'm about to choke from the heat!
The air!
He's taking everything from me!
Damn you, royal!
Now, flame-binding magic, Leo home!
I had to stamp out this evil, even if the vice-captain's body was damaged.
You're back!
Thank you.
We're saved!
Surf by Tholeon!
You really are the greatest magic knight there is!
Hurry!
Help the injured!
Right!
That was awesome!
My brother still got it!
I'm going to be even better one of these days, though!
As your captain, I solemnly vowed that she will be returned to your former self.
Oh, yeah!
While you were out of commission, our sister became the captain!
She what?
Is this true?
Um, yes, sir.
That's what happened, former Captain Foigolion!
Our sister, eh?
She should have been our captain in the first place.
But she couldn't even be bothered to join the magic knights.
Seems I've forced her to act out of character.
Salamander has made me aware of the sinister, non-human magic power that's been permeating the royal capital.
While I've been asleep, the situation's intensified a great deal.
When the eye of the midnight sun ransacked the city that day, I knew that I was the person they were targeting.
That's why I decided to play right into their hands.
Strange.
What is this place?
It's you!
This mana?
William Vangent's?
I don't understand.
It appears you've arrived.
I had hoped you would surmise our plan and not come here.
I prayed for that.
Please explain yourself.
Tell me the truth.
What plan?
You will see.
Quite soon, in fact.
What is happening to you?
No one knows my secret.
Not even the Wizard King who gave me my mask.
But you will understand things when you see the other me.
Enough of this nonsense.
Who are you?
And what have you done to William?
Interesting.
The captain of the Crimson Lion Kings.
You're normally so collected.
But now even you seem shaken.
All I need is an instant.
Get him.
I have so many questions.
Why didn't he kill me when he had the chance?
Who was that person?
And what has become of William?
However,
I won't be the word of this matter until I can ascertain the truth.
Crimson Lion Kings!
Clover Kingdom is in grave danger.
We must end this bloodshed.
With the fires of strength and pride that burn deep within our hearts,
we will strive to vanquish the enemy.
Hurrah!
The real fight is just beginning.
Hmm.
These outfits are awfully similar to the garment worn by that human royal.
That's strange, isn't it?
I'm sure the person who gathered us here made that decision.
Talk about a sick sense of humor.
I'm not sure I follow you.
They expect us to wipe out the human race, obviously.
Right, that's simple enough.
After all, the humans killed us,
and they've been living the good life ever since without a care in the world.
We've got more than enough reason to be upset, if you ask me.
Oh, I see you made it.
Well, well, well.
The gang's all here.
I was trapped in a pretty strange place when I awakened.
But I had fun getting out.
Humans infuriate me.
Always so smug in their stupidity.
I'm assuming your cousin was the one who brought us together, right, Lahtry?
Correct.
This is all Potry's doing.
Birds of a twisted feather flock together, I suppose.
And now I'm itching to get my hands around the throats of those despicable royal scum.
The midnight sun is set.
It's time to show humankind the wrath of a brand new golden dawn.
Brother.
Are you there?
Longris?
You're back to normal!
I'm so glad!
Wait up!
Hey, come back!
Please don't leave!
Longris!
What the heck was that?
And where am I?
Is my name even Fenral anymore?
How long were you planning to snooze, numbskull?
Captain Yummy?
As you can see, things aren't going too well out there.
You felt it, right?
That evil, inhuman power that your brother was giving off?
The stuff is everywhere now.
Okay, then.
Let's go.
Longris.
I'm gonna save you this time.
Long.
Longris.
K
?
SEAD
These are all my simple energy.
How do you feel, I didn't know.
I'm sorry to be wrong.
I don't know.
If you're in a dream,
I just cry out loud.
I'm sorry to be wrong.
Kazashita chinkai hikari ga nikiru treasure
A man who refuses to suffer a single misplaced hair
Um, not that it matters right now, but your hair looks great
In that case, there's something else I'm meant to do
Right?
Come on, seriously
A man who lovingly brushes every tooth not once, but three times
Okay, I'm sure your mouth is clean enough, sir
Well then, there's yet another thing I'm meant to do
Five more minutes, please
All right, this is ridiculous
Fuegolion Vermillion, a man who diligently achieves his beauty, Rastan
Enough of this foolishness, this is no laughing matter
I am the steadfast captain of the crimson lion kings, Fuegolion Vermillion
Black Clover, page 99
The desperate path towards survival
I'm sorry, did you just call me former captain?